<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Petrus&#39; Webpage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Petrus&#39; Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 22:13:56 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on One Piece&#39;s Rocks Xebec Flashback</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-piece-xebec-flashback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 22:13:56 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-piece-xebec-flashback/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;thoughts-on-one-pieces-rocks-xebec-flashback&#34;&gt;Thoughts on One Piece&amp;rsquo;s Rocks Xebec Flashback&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dude, this thing is so great.&#xA;Since June 23 this year with One Piece chapter 1152, we are having a huge plot on Rocks D. Xebec (or Rocks D. Jones now we know it), learning more of what happened on the God Valley incident, discovering why Garp is not so hypocrite as we thought even if he&amp;rsquo;s a marine and more on Rocks&amp;rsquo; crew. I got my heart really warming on Rayleigh and Shakki relationship that I almost cried when he saved her. That remembers me when she told the Strawhat&amp;rsquo;s crew that he is always looking for women, but we never saw Rayleigh having that kind of attitude - that is clearly Shakki being totally jealous about him!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first personal website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 23:22:25 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is my first attempt on making a personal blog and being part of an actually human internet. Here is where I can express my thoughts, share ideas and links without being supressed by the weird big tech algorithym that enhances the crapiest form of liquifying your brain with the most stupid content, from dumb memes like tralalelo tralala (well, when I was 10, the MLG illuminati snoop dogg smoke weed everyday brainrot was also pretty good, but now I&amp;rsquo;m grown up lol). There is also some random AI generated articles from actual bots that if you google their name, it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;person&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; that makes content about gaming, cooking, politics and sharks (definitly cool, but not a real specialist haha).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
