<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
	<title>Petrus&#39; Webpage</title>
	<link>http://localhost:1313/tags/</link>
	<description>Recent content in Tags on Petrus&#39; Webpage</description>
	<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
	<language>en-us</language>
    
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	
	
	<item>
		<title>My first personal website</title>
		<link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 23:22:25 -0300</pubDate>
		
		<guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
		<description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is my first attempt on making a personal blog and being part of an actually human internet. Here is where I can express my thoughts, share ideas and links without being supressed by the weird big tech algorithym that enhances the crapiest form of liquifying your brain with the most stupid content, from dumb memes like tralalelo tralala (well, when I was 10, the MLG illuminati snoop dogg smoke weed everyday brainrot was also pretty good, but now I&amp;rsquo;m grown up lol). There is also some random AI generated articles from actual bots that if you google their name, it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;person&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; that makes content about gaming, cooking, politics and sharks (definitly cool, but not a real specialist haha).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-i-like-and-what-you-are-gonna-see-here&#34;&gt;What I like and what you are gonna see here&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here I will be fixing most of this original css and start making some content on my interests, like nerd stuff, anime, manga, linux, programming, gaming and whatever I find cool to share and express my ideas on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-i-came-up-with-this&#34;&gt;How I came up with this&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site is made using &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;, a static website generator, and who introduced me to use it was &lt;a href=&#34;https://lukesmith.xyz&#34;&gt;Luke Smith&lt;/a&gt; that makes youtube content on his personal interests of linux and sharing about free and opensource software which uses Hugo to code his blog too. He talked several times about how the dead internet is made by the algorithym that makes the stupid bot content prevail and that YOU should make the internet alive having your own webspace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-beauty-of-this-indie-web-thing&#34;&gt;The beauty of this &amp;ldquo;indie web&amp;rdquo; thing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I&amp;rsquo;m a programmer and I know a bit of how internet works and I write code, so it&amp;rsquo;s not difficult for me to code this site and whatever, but something that is a real charm for me is the people from &lt;a href=&#34;https://neocities.org&#34;&gt;Neocities&lt;/a&gt; that learnt to code just to make their own websites and there are even some people who use simplified tools for blogging like this. I really enjoy people learning new things to make their own personal stuff from ground up. You should checkout some really interesting people like &lt;a href=&#34;https://solaria.neocities.org&#34;&gt;Solaria&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://yesterweb.org&#34;&gt;Yesterweb&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://thricegreat.neocities.org&#34;&gt;Thricegreat&lt;/a&gt;. They having really different content, but that is the best part, their websites are REALLY unique and it reflects their own personality in a way that you get comfy visiting someone&amp;rsquo;s own space and not someone&amp;rsquo;s x/instagram/facebook/reddit profile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it for today and I hope to finish this website aesthetic and css soon (I used to hate css, cause I&amp;rsquo;m a backend and command line guy, but I&amp;rsquo;m getting used to it) and post more content here. Hope you liked and make sure to bookmark me to come around in the future!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>
